So, OK, two glasses
forming liquids.
One glass is formed.
Plot the molar volume
versus temperature.
All right, so now, let's see.
How about this?
Could this be the volume
per mole versus temperature?
So I'm going to try it out here.
I'm going to go like this.
I'm going to go like this, and
that looks like the liquid,
maybe.
And then I'm going to go
like this and maybe this,
and we'll call that T1.
Does that look right?
No, this can't be right.
This can't be right because,
you see, I said that T1,
this is a glass transition.
That's a glass transition.
That's a Tg.
That's another Tg.
But I've said in the question
T1 is greater than Tm.
Well, so this can't be true
because Tm has to be out here.
Tm is out here where there's
a different transition that
occurs, and it turns
into a crystal.
So this couldn't be
right, T1 greater than Tm.